{"name": "US State Capitals", "card_prefix": "", "cards": [{"id": 1, "front": "Alabama", "back": "Montgomery", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564328.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549928.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 2, "front": "Alaska", "back": "Juneau", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564330.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549930.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 3, "front": "Arizona", "back": "Phoenix", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564334.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549934.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 4, "front": "Arkansas", "back": "Little Rock", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564336.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549936.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 5, "front": "California", "back": "Sacramento", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564340.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549940.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 6, "front": "Colorado", "back": "Denver", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564343.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549943.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 7, "front": "Connecticut", "back": "Hartford", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564345.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549945.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 8, "front": "Delaware", "back": "Dover", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564347.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549947.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 9, "front": "Florida", "back": "Tallahassee", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564351.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549951.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 10, "front": "Georgia", "back": "Atlanta", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564354.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549954.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 11, "front": "Hawaii", "back": "Honolulu", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564357.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549957.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 12, "front": "Idaho", "back": "Boise", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564359.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549959.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 13, "front": "Illinois", "back": "Springfield", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564362.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549962.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 14, "front": "Indiana", "back": "Indianapolis", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564365.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549965.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 15, "front": "Iowa", "back": "Des Moines", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686566281.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549968.0, "result": false}, {"timestamp": 1686551881.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 0.5}}}, {"id": 16, "front": "Kansas", "back": "Topeka", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564370.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549970.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 17, "front": "Kentucky", "back": "Frankfort", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564374.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549974.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 18, "front": "Louisiana", "back": "Baton Rouge", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564377.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686549977.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 19, "front": "Maine", "back": "Augusta", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564420.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550020.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 20, "front": "Maryland", "back": "Annapolis", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564423.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550023.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 21, "front": "Massachusetts", "back": "Boston", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564426.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550026.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 22, "front": "Michigan", "back": "Lansing", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564429.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550029.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 23, "front": "Minnesota", "back": "Saint Paul", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564432.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550032.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 24, "front": "Mississippi", "back": "Jackson", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564436.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550036.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 25, "front": "Missouri", "back": "Jefferson City", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564453.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550053.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 26, "front": "Montana", "back": "Helena", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564460.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550060.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 27, "front": "Nebraska", "back": "Lincoln", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564462.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550062.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 28, "front": "Nevada", "back": "Carson City", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564465.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550065.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 29, "front": "New Hampshire", "back": "Concord", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564480.0, "current_streak": -1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550080.0, "result": false}], "accuracy": 0.0}}}, {"id": 30, "front": "New Jersey", "back": "Trenton", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564483.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550083.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 31, "front": "New Mexico", "back": "Santa Fe", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564485.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550085.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 32, "front": "New York", "back": "Albany", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564487.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550087.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 33, "front": "North Carolina", "back": "Raleigh", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564490.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550090.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 34, "front": "North Dakota", "back": "Bismarck", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564493.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550093.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 35, "front": "Ohio", "back": "Columbus", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564496.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550096.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 36, "front": "Oklahoma", "back": "Oklahoma City", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564499.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550099.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 37, "front": "Oregon", "back": "Salem", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564502.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550102.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 38, "front": "Pennsylvania", "back": "Harrisburg", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564521.0, "current_streak": -1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550121.0, "result": false}], "accuracy": 0.0}}}, {"id": 39, "front": "Rhode Island", "back": "Providence", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564526.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550126.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 40, "front": "South Carolina", "back": "Columbia", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564529.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550129.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 41, "front": "South Dakota", "back": "Pierre", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564545.0, "current_streak": -1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550145.0, "result": false}], "accuracy": 0.0}}}, {"id": 42, "front": "Tennessee", "back": "Nashville", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564550.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550150.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 43, "front": "Texas", "back": "Austin", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564551.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550151.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 44, "front": "Utah", "back": "Salt Lake City", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564555.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550155.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 45, "front": "Vermont", "back": "Montpelier", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564559.0, "current_streak": -1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550159.0, "result": false}], "accuracy": 0.0}}}, {"id": 46, "front": "Virginia", "back": "Richmond", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564563.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550163.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 47, "front": "Washington", "back": "Olympia", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564566.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550166.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 48, "front": "West Virginia", "back": "Charleston", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564570.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550170.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 49, "front": "Wisconsin", "back": "Madison", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564572.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550172.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}, {"id": 50, "front": "Wyoming", "back": "Cheyenne", "recall_data": {"next_due": 1686564576.0, "current_streak": 1, "history": {"data": [{"timestamp": 1686550176.0, "result": true}], "accuracy": 1.0}}}]}